Guide to the New York University Archives Photograph Collection PHOTO.00001
New York University Archives
- Student Life
  - Students in WSP - Youth Leadership Training Program, cuid17773 (Box 315)
- Tisch School of the Arts
  - Advisement - Classroom Scenes, cuid17644 (Box 1)
  - Communication Arts - Dressing Room, cuid17645 (Box 2)
  - Dance Classes, cuid17646 (Box 3)
  - Dance performances, cuid17647 (Box 4)
  - Dance contacts, cuid17648 (Box 5)
  - Dean's office - Dramatic writing, cuid17649 (Box 6)
  - Drama-contact prints, cuid17650 (Box 7)
  - Drama performances - Film Faculty, cuid17651 (Box 8)
  - Film Faculty - Future Filmmakers Program, cuid17652 (Box 9)
  - Film and TV contacts, cuid17653 (Box 10)
  - Film and Television program - Graduate Acting Program Workshops, cuid17654 (Box 11)
  - Make-up class - Movie stills, cuid17655 (Box 12)
  - Movement class - Singing, cuid17656 (Box 13)
  - Special events, cuid17657 (Box 14)
  - Contacts-Stage Design - Theatre Design, cuid17658 (Box 15)
- University Heights
  - Nichols Hall -- Negative, 1928; cuid17597 (Box Nitrate)
  - Philosophy Hall -- Negative, 1922; cuid17598 (Box Nitrate)
  - Private Houses, Kimball -- Negative, 1924; cuid17599 (Box Nitrate)
  - Brown House -- Negative, 1925; cuid17600 (Box Nitrate)
  - University College from River -- Negative, 1921; cuid17601 (Box Nitrate)
  - Electrolier at Library -- Negative, 1922; cuid17602 (Box Nitrate)
  - Gould Library Doors
    - Gould Library Doors 1 -- Negative, 1921; cuid17603 (Box Nitrate)
    - Gould Library Doors 2 -- Negative, 1921; cuid17604 (Box Nitrate)
    - Gould Library Doors 3 -- Negative, undated; cuid17605 (Box Nitrate)
  - Graduate Hall
    - Graduate Hall -- Negative, 1925; cuid17606 (Box 482)
    - Graduate Hall -- Negative, 1926; cuid17607 (Box Nitrate)
  - Biological Laboratories -- Negative, 1924; cuid17608 (Box Nitrate)
  - Hall of Philosophy -- Negative, 1926; cuid17609 (Box Nitrate)
  - University Heights Campus Bridge -- Negative, 1926; cuid17610 (Box Nitrate)
  - Eastman Pyrometal Tank
    - Eastman Pyrometal Tank 1 -- Negative, 1926; cuid17611 (Box Nitrate)
    - Eastman Pyrometal Tank 2 -- Negative, 1928; cuid17612 (Box Nitrate)
  - Fountain -- Negative, 1921; cuid17613 (Box 482)
  - Lipton Flag Mast -- Negative, 1925; cuid17614 (Box 482)
  - Gould Memorial Library
    - Gould Memorial Library 1 -- Negative, undated; cuid17615 (Box 482)
    - Gould Memorial Library 2 -- Negative, undated; cuid17616 (Box 482)
    - Gould Memorial Library 3 -- Negative, undated; cuid17617
  - Gould Hall -- Negative, undated; cuid17618 (Box 482)
  - University Heights Neighborhood -- Negative, 1926; cuid17619 (Box Nitrate)
  - University Heights Neighborhood from Hall of Fame -- Negative, 1926; cuid17620 (Box Nitrate)
  - Aerial View of University Heights Campus and Neighborhood 1 -- Negative, 1938; cuid17621 (Box Nitrate)
  - Aerial View of University Heights Campus and Neighborhood 2 -- Negative, undated; cuid17622
  - Power House -- Negative, 1926; cuid17623 (Box Nitrate)
  - South Hall
    - South Hall 1 -- Negative, 1926; cuid17624 (Box Nitrate)
    - South Hall 2 -- Negative, 1926; cuid17625 (Box Nitrate)
  - New Grandstand -- Negative, 1925; cuid17626 (Box 482)
  - General Views - unidentified, cuid17862 (Box 427)
  - Gould Library, cuid17863 (Box 428)
  - Oversized - Gould Student Center, cuid17864 (Box 429)
  - Dean Thorndike Saville - General Views, cuid17865 (Box 430)
  - General Views, cuid17866 (Box 432, Box 434)
  - Aerial views, cuid17867 (Box 433, Box 435)
  - Aerospace laboratory - Biology Laboratories, cuid17868 (Box 436)
  - Bliss Engineering Laboratory - Engineering WW II Photo Album, cuid17869 (Box 437)
  - Engineering - Gould Hall of Technology, cuid17870 (Box 438)
  - Gould Library, Exteriors - Gould Library, Stanford White Memorial Doors, cuid17902 (Box 476)
  - Gould Library interiors, cuid17871 (Box 439)
  - Gould Library, exteriors - Gould House, cuid17872 (Box 440)
  - Gould Student Center, cuid17873 (Box 441)
  - Green Laboratory - Guggenheim School of Aeronautics, cuid17874 (Box 442)
  - Gymnasium, cuid17875 (Box 443)
  - Hall of Fame, cuid17876 (Box 444)
  - Hall of Fame, cuid17877 (Box 445, Box 446, Box 447, Box 448, Box 449)
  - Havermeyer Hall of Chemistry - Knoop Sculpture, cuid17878 (Box 450)
  - Laboratories - Machinery, cuid17879 (Box 451)
  - Mali Estate, cuid17880 (Box 452)
  - Neighborhood - Negatives, cuid17881 (Box 453)
  - Nichols Building, cuid17882 (Box 454)
  - Plans - Silver Residence Hall, cuid17883 (Box 455)
  - Sonic Boom Lab - YMCA, cuid17884 (Box 456)
  - Schwab House and Estate, cuid17885 (Box 457)
  - World War II Engineering album, cuid17886 (Box 458)
- Vanderbilt Hall/Law School
  - Artist's renderings - Exteriors, cuid17742 (Box 251, Box 252, Box 253)
- Wagner Graduate School of Public Service
  - Special Events - Students, cuid17693 (Box 50)
- Weinstein Center for Student Living
  - Construction site - Sculpture, cuid17743 (Box 254, Box 255, Box 256, Box 257)
- Non-NYU Subjects
  - Landmark Buildings, cuid17887 (Box 459)
  - Aerial views of NYC - Atomic Bomb Drill, cuid17888 (Box 460)
  - Barnes & Noble - City Skylines, cuid17889 (Box 461)
  - City Scenes, cuid17890 (Box 462, Box 463)
  - Clinton Court - Garment District, cuid17891 (Box 464)
  - Goulandris Museum - Manhattan street scenes, cuid17892 (Box 465)
  - Map of NYC - NY Police, cuid17893 (Box 466)
  - NYPL - Presidents, cuid17894 (Box 467)
  - Radio City Music Hall - Soho, cuid17895 (Box 468)
  - South Church - Telephones, cuid17896 (Box 469)
  - Theatre District - Yellow Brick Road, cuid17897 (Box 470)
- Miscellaneous
  - Illustrations, cuid17899 (Box 472)
  - Digital photos on physical media, cuid17900 (Box 474)
  - Separated photos, RG 4.2, RG 9.7, cuid17901 (Box 475)
  - Group photos at an awards ceremony, undated; cuid17971 (Box Shared University Archives 042, Folder 1)
  - Photograph of building labeled "To Julius Silver with gratitude and appreciation from the staff of the Institute", undated; cuid17973 (Box Shared University Archives 042, Folder 4)
  - Photos pulled for Oliva exhibit, cuid17974 (Box 475)
  - Senior Ball, 1934; cuid17975 (Box Shared University Archives 091, Folder 8)
  - Negative Used to Print Book on School of Science Labs -- Negative, 1925; cuid17636 (Box Nitrate)
  - Untitled -- Negative, 1915; cuid17637 (Box Nitrate)
- Portrait Files
  - Albert Sheppard -- Negative, undated; cuid17590 (Box Nitrate)
  - E.G. Hesser -- Negative, undated; cuid17591 (Box Nitrate)
  - Alvin Busse -- Negative, undated; cuid17592 (Box Nitrate)
  - Herbert M. Schiffer -- Negative, undated; cuid17593 (Box Nitrate)
  - Charles Pieper -- Negative, undated; cuid17594 (Box Nitrate)
- Hall of Fame
  - College Insignia on Large Fountain at Hall of Fame - Exteriors -- Negative, 1921; cuid17630 (Box Nitrate)
  - Fountain at Hall of Fame - Exteriors -- Negative, 1921; cuid17631 (Box Nitrate)
  - Fountain at Hall of Fame - Exteriors -- Negative, 1922; cuid17632 (Box Nitrate)
  - Looking Across Palisades from Hall of Fame - Exteriors -- Negative, 1926; cuid17633 (Box Nitrate)
  - Hall of Fame, Sedgwick Avenue - Exteriors -- Negative, 1928; cuid17634 (Box Nitrate)
  - Hall of Fame -- Negative, 1928; cuid17635 (Box Nitrate)
  - Hall of Fame Bust Unveiling Ceremony, 1930; cuid17643 (Box Shared University Archives 004)
- Commencement (Box Commencement_Negs1, Box Commencement_Negs2)